Finding Aid for the Waldo Salt Papers, 1936-1987
UCLA Library, Performing Arts Special Collections
- PERSONAL MATERIALS
  - FAMILY PAPERS
      - Condolence letters and cards to W.Salt for Gladys Schwartz Salt's death, 1980. 38 items. (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence regarding headstone for Gladys Schwartz Salt's grave at Riverside Cemetery (Rochelle Park, New Jersey), 1980. 7 items. (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Gladys Schwartz's personal documents, 1946-80. Incl: six passports; marriage, divorce and death certificates; teaching accreditations; etc. 33 items. (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Legal correspondence regarding the estate of Gladys Schwartz Salt, 1980-81. 8 items. (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Deeds to property of W.Salt and Gladys Schwartz Salt, 1970-78. 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Letters and photographs from Donna Titcomb, [grandaughter of W.Salt's brother William?], 1983. 4 items. (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Christmas card from Patricia L[ynn] Titcomb, [grandaughter of W.Salt's brother William?], n.d. (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Invitation from Mary Lynn Titcomb, [grandaughter of W.Salt's brother William?], to attend commencement ceremony at Branham High School, (San Jose, California), l978. (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - FINANCIAL-LEGAL
      - Legal correspondence with George Litto Agency, Inc., Bart/Levy Associates, Inc., and Creative Artists Agency, regarding contracts and representation, 1964-83. 8 items. (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Petty cash receipts and copies of itemized expenses for W.Salt and Jennorah Productions, Inc., 1984-86. (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence with United Airlines, incl. award notifications, 1983-84; correspondence with American Express regarding cash program and insurance plan, 1981-85; list detailing content of "Additional credit card box" and "wallet". 9 items. (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence with attorney George T. Altman concerning W.Salt taxes, May-June 1952. 4 items. (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence with accounting firm Gerwin, Jamner & Pariser, regarding management of W.Salt's finances, 1977-1985. 6 items. (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence regarding W.Salt's partnership of Han Lani Farms, Hawaii, 1982-86. 9 items. (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Legal correspondence concerning Jennorah Productions, Inc., incl. copy of contracts and letters from law firm Ball, Hunt, Hart, Brown and Baerwitz, l977-81. 7 items. (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Legal correspondence concerning W.Salt's involvement in various judicial cases, incl. letters by attorneys, notifications, depositions, etc., 1962-67. 9 items. (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Legal letter from attorney Murray C. Lertzman discussing alimony and child-support, 9/11/67; notification by the California Department of Motor Vehicle concerning hearing about W.Salt's driving permit, 1/14/66. (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence with the Social Security Administration, regarding health care, 1979-80. (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Contract between Leeds Music Corporation, Roy Webb and W.Salt to compose original scores and lyrics, 1/7/48. (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Letters from Screen Gems, Inc., to M.L.Davenport (pseudonym), concerning payment for television scripts "King of the Jewel Thieves", "The Tidal Wave", "Scared Witness", "The Gasparilla", and music for "Ivanhoe", June 1958-April 1959. 9 items. (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Legal correspondence regarding W.Salt's partnership agreement in stage play "A Raisin in the Sun", October 1958-April 1961. 19 items. (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Business certificate for partnership between W.Salt and Earl Robinson, under the designation of "Music Hall Productions", August 1953. (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Copy of separation agreement between W.Salt and his wife Mary Davenport Salt, unsigned, 1964; copy of trust indenture made between W.Salt and his wife, unsigned, l964. (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence and records regarding W.Salt's financial situation, 1937-51. Incl: records of payments, loans, purchases, bank transactions, receipts, etc. (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence with Bernard Skadron, W.Salt's business manager, 1951-52. 14 items. (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Accounting ledger from January 1944 through January 1950. (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Four sheets with trial balances for l950; copy of receipt from Mitchell Frug, W.Salt's business manager, regarding W. and Mary Salt's financial records, 1950. (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Accounting ledger for 1951. (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Accounting ledger for l955. (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Accounting ledger for l956 and 1957. (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Tax records from 1938 through 1956. (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Insurance records from 1940 through 1953. (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and records regarding purchase and lease of property, escrows, loans, mortgages, etc., 1939-53. (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Records of paid bills, l950-51. (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Records and payroll tax reports for employer/employee, 1948. (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Records of dues paid to the Screen Writers' Guild, 1946-49. (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Promisory note signed by W.Salt on behalf of the Harold Hecht Company and Norma Productions, 6/8/51. (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1947. Incl: bank statements; deposit slips for checks from RKO Pictures, Inc. (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1948. Incl: check stubs with annotations on the back regarding check deposits and payments by RKO Pictures, Inc., etc.; typed lists of checks, dates and payees. (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1948. Incl: bank statements; deposit slips for checks from RKO Pictures, Inc. (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1949. Incl: bank statements; deposit slips for checks from Norma Productions. (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1949. Incl: cancelled checks; hand-written and typed lists with annotations. (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1949. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Transactions with Security- First National Bank of Los Angeles, 1950. Incl: deposit slips for checks from RKO Pictures, Inc., and Norma Productions; typed statements of account. (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Transactions with Security- First National Bank of Los Angeles and Bank of America, 1950. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1950. Incl: bank statements; check stubs; cancelled checks. (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Transactions with Security- First National Bank of Los Angeles, 1950. Incl: bank statements; cancelled checks. (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Transactions with Security- First National Bank of Los Angeles, 1950-51. Incl: check stubs. (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, 1951. Incl: bank statements. (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, 1953. Incl: bank statements; records of deposits. (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, July-November 1951. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, April-September 1952. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, December 1951-April 1952. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Transactions with The Chase National Bank, September 1952- July 1953. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Transactions with Chemical Bank, 1954. Incl: bank statements, cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Transactions with First National City Bank, September 1956-April 1957. Incl: cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1947-49. Incl: check stubs, cancelled checks. (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Transactions with Bank of America, 1941-50. Incl: savings account book. (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Transactions with Security- First National Bank of Los Angeles, 1951. Incl: check stubs, deposit slips, bank statements. (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Transactions with Bankers Trust Company, 1955. Incl: records of deposits and checks drawn. (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Transactions with The First National City Bank of New York, 1956 and 1959. Incl: check stubs and deposit slips for payments by Screen Gems, Inc., with two letters signed by Benedict Berenberg, regarding payment for scripts in "Stakeout" TV series. (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Transactions with Chemical Corn Exchange Bank, July-December 1956. Incl: deposit slips. (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Check stubs from unidentified bank, 1954-56. (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - MEDICAL
      - W.Salt's medical history, as a patient of Dr.Murray Abowitz, 1945-79. Incl: two folders marked "chart #1" and "chart #2". (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - W.Salt's medical history, 1983-85. (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Allergy tests, 1986. (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Medical report on eye hemorrhage, 1986. (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Stay at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center due to heart and lungs condition, l986. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Knee surgery at Beverly Hills Medical Center, l983. (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Respiratory care at W.Salt's home in Santa Monica, 1987. (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Triple by-pass surgery at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, l980. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - MISCELLANEOUS
      - W.Salt's calendar/appointment book for l974. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - NOTEBOOKS
      - Notes and sketches for film and television projects, incl. drawings, n.d. (List on front page). (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Notes, sketches and drawings for "The Artful Dodger", "Mr.Broadway" and other projects, incl. two drawings by Frances Lardner, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Typed and hand-written notes and sketches for various projects, n.d. (Loose pages). (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - PHOTOS
      - Individual shots of W.Salt. b/w and color, various sizes; undated. 8 photos and 1 contact sheet. (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Portrait shots of W.Salt. b/w, for passport; undated. 11 photos and 1 negative. (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Photo of William Salt, Sr. -W.Salt's father-. b/w, 5x7; undated. (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Portrait shot of Mary Davenport Salt -W.Salt's wife. b/w, 4x6, undated; group shot with Mary Davenport, her mother, her two daughters -Deborah and Jennifer- and grandson Jonah. color, 3/4, undated. (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Individual and group shots with Jennifer and Deborah Salt -W.Salt's daughters. b/w and color, various sizes; some are inscribed on the back, undated. 13 photos. (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Individual and group shots with Jennifer Salt, incl. her son Jonah, W.Salt, John Schlesinger, etc. b/w, color, various sizes; some are inscribed on the back and dated. 40 photos. (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Individual and group shots with Deborah Salt, incl. W.Salt, other relatives and friends. b/w and color, various sizes; some are inscribed on the back and dated. 30 photos. (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Individual and group shots with Gladys Schwartz Salt -W.Salt's wife-, incl. W.Salt, her parents Simon and Anna Schwartz, other relatives and friends. b/w and color, various sizes; some inscribed on the back and dated. 81 photos and 9 contact sheets. (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Photos taken by Gladys Schwartz Salt (some experiment with light and shapes). color, 3/4; undated. 103 phots. (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - lst wife-, incl. W.Salt and her son Guy, l981 and 1982. 3 photos. (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Photo of W.Salt and director John Landis, ("early 1980"); production stills for film "Into the Night", directed by J.Landis, with Jeff Goldblum and Michelle Pfeiffer, and W.Salt in cameo role. b/w and color, 8x10. 5 photos. (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Photo of W.Salt and Ring Lardner, Jr., taken during W.Salt and Eve Merriam's wedding, 1983. color, 4x6. (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Photos of W.Salt and Earl Robinson. b/w, 8x10, [1952?]; color, 3x4, l982. (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Production still of John Schlesinger and Jerome Hellman in the set of "Midnight Cowboy", [1969]. b/w, 8x10. (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Individual and group shots with W.Salt dressed as a rabbi for film directed by Melanie Mayron, l985. color, 4x5. 4 photos. (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Group shots with W.Salt and various people, some identified. b/w and color, various sizes; some dated on the back. 10 photos. (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Photos without W.Salt. color, 3x4; some inscribed and dated on the back. 35 photos. (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Photos without W.Salt. b/w and color, various sizes; some identified and dated on the back. 34 photos. (Box 107, Folder 12)
      - Group shot with W.Salt at Stanford University. b/w, 6x9; undated. (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Photographs of W.Salt, family and friends, taken in his Connecticut home, [1970s]. b/w and color, various sizes; some are inscribed on the back and dated. 90 photos, 1 contact sheet, 1 slide, and negatives. (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Five contact sheets and negatives of trip to Spain and Morocco, and of W.Salt and family in Connecticut, [1970s]. (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Photos and negatives of trip to Guatemala, 1975. color, 3x4. 132 photos. (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Photos of trip to Greece, [1976]. color, 3x4. More than 330 photos. (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Photos of W.Salt and Eve Merriam's wedding, with family and friends (identified on the back), 1983. color, 4x6. 12 photos. (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Photos of W.Salt and various people (some identified) at Sundance Institute (Utah), 1981, 1985 and 1986. b/w and color, various sizes. 10 photos. (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Photos of W.Salt's family and friends, taken at his home after the memorial service, March 1987. color, 4x4. 5 photos. (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Negatives, unnumbered. (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Two portrait shots of W.Salt, n.d. b/w, 11x14. (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Three photos of Jennifer Salt, n.d. b/w, 11x14. (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Photo of Deborah Salt, 1960. b/w, 11x14. (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Portrait shots of Gladys Schwartz Salt, n.d. b/w, 11x14. 14 photos. (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Portrait shot of John Schlesinger, n.d. b/w, 10x13. (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Photo of couple in a beach, n.d. b/w, 11x14; photo of Andalusian house [?], n.d. color, 8x10. (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - PROJECTS NOT AUTHORED BY WALDO SALT
      - "The Black and White Handbook for Beginners", poem by Billie Allen and Nan Lanier. Typed script, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - "Futures", treatment for a screenplay by David Berry, 1986, 14p. Incl. copy of letter from American Playhouse to Tom Bird, Artistic Director Vietnam Veterans Ensemble Theatre, 7/28/86. (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - "The Now of the Children", story outline by O.S. Barron, l968, 42p. Note on cover: "Property of Julian Bercovici". (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - "Hedda According to Strindberg", screenplay by Leonardo Bercovici, n.d., 113p. (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - "A Spongeful of Vinegar", screenplay by Arthur Paul Burns, 1966, 162p. (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - "A Plea, a Confession, a List, and Assorted Vagaries", by Arthur Birnkrant, n.d., 134p. (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - "Rainbow Gold", screenplay by Ayoka Chenzira. Two versions: one dated l984 (110p), the other 1985 (90p). (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - "A Little Rebellion", treatment for a screenplay by Joshua Daniel, n.d., 14p. Incl: letter to W.Salt by the author, 2/24/85; tape of interviews with Joshua Daniel. (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - "TD", treatment for a screenplay by Joshua Daniel, n.d., 33p. (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - "Child's Play", screenplay ("rough draft") by Carol Doumani, l986, 116p. (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - "Artist's Proof", screenplay by Carol Doumani, n.d., 127p. (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - "Cape Town", screenplay/treatment by Bernard Clegg and Robert McKee, n.d., 107p. (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - "Going Back. A Return to Vietnam", [dialogue and continuity for documentary] by producer/director David Munro, with Vietnam veterans Bob Muller, Tom Bird, Michael Harbert and John Terzano, n.d., 72p. (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - "Raisin in the Sun", drama in three acts by Lorraine Hansberry, l957. Typed script, annotated, various pagings. (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - "Les Blancs", play by Lorraine Hansberry, l969. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - "Smart Money", screenplay ("final draft") by Gary Jenneke and Steve Larson, from a story by them and John Hanson, n.d., 110p. (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - "Hidden China", documentary project, l986. Typed script, no paging. (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - "Fire on the Water. Dispatches from the Kid's War": scene outline, character sketches and synopsis by Robert Hillman, n.d., no paging; "Out of Sight!": scene outline [by Robert Hillman], n.d., no paging. (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - "Hugger-mugger", by Paul Jarrico, [198?], 10p. Story idea for a film based on the making of "Salt of the Earth". (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - "The Last Refuge", play in three acts by Paul Jarrico, n.d. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - "Stacking", screenplay by Victoria Jenkins. Two versions: one, "revised second draft" (March 1984, 115p), the other, "fourth draft" (September l984, 98p). (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - "The Great Goddess: Lady of the Beasts", essay by Buffie Johnson, n.d. Typed script, 131p. (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - "Fade Away", screenplay by Janet Dulin Jones. Two versions: one, "revised first draft" (May 1986, 160p), the other undated (130p). (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - "Peter's Project", treatment ("Fourth Draft") by Harriet Karr, 1983, 12p. (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - "Letting Go", screenplay by Harriet Karr, n.d., 100p. (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - "The Revolutionary", screenplay by Hans Koningsberger, 1969, 169p. (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - "Going the Distance", screenplay by Kate Lardner, l984, 105p. (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - "Touches of oneness", poems by Lannie Lasky. Typed script, n.d., 189p. (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - "The Kin of Ata", screenplay by Marika Lumi. Two versions: one undated (128p), the other dated 1983, 71p. (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - "The Good Life: Lady Macbeth of Westport", play by Eve Merriam, n.d. Typed script, no paging. (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - "The Lucifer Game", musical by Eve Merriam and Robin Wagner, lyrics by Eve Merriam, music by Helen Miller, n.d. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - "Acadian Waltz", screenplay ("fifth draft") by Glen Pitre, 1983, 101p. (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - "Los Alamos", screenplay ("first draft") by Bruce Robinson, n.d., 214p. (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - "Theron Ware", play by Phil Rorig, n.d. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - "Illinois People. A Dramatic Cantata", music and text by Earl Robinson, lyrics by Carl Haverlin, n.d. Typed script, 21p. (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - "Song of Atlantis", play by Earl Robinson, l983. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - "Ballad of the Gentle Ones. A Fantasie, a Communing, Dolphin to Human", by Earl Robinson, n.d. Typed script, annotated, various pagings. (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - "I Been Thinkin' About J.C.", [cantata?] by Earl Robinson, n.d. Typed script, no paging. (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - "David of Sassoun. A Fairytale, a Musical Legend, an Epic Pageant, an Opera?", by Earl Robinson, n.d. Typed script, annotated, various pagings. Incl. note to W.Salt by the author, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - "The Surgeon of Kiev", novel by William Haslem Salt, Sr., n.d. Typed script, various pagings. (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - "The Last Romantic", screenplay by Jack Skinner, n.d., 120p. (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - "The Wartime Correspondence of an American Family. March 1944-November 1945", by Jane Levy Troy, incl. introduction by J.L.Troy; transcription of letters; copies of photos. Various pagings. (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - "Holding Together. The World War II Correspondence of an American Family", ed. by Jane Levy Troy. Typed script, incl. foreword, family tree, transcription of letters, photos, etc. Note on cover: "I". pp. 1-300. (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - "Holding Together. The World War II Correspondence of an American Family", ed. by Jane Levy Troy. Typed script, incl. foreword, family tree, transcription of letters, photos, etc. [II] pp. 301-590. (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - "After Death", screenplay by Paul Williams, 1983, 123p. (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - "Yes, Sir, That's My Baby", screenplay ("second draft") by Blanche Ziegler, l983, 120p. (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - "Deep Purple", screenplay by Blanche Ziegler, ("property of Karen Black"). Two versions, both dated March l985: one 115p, the other has note on cover: "revised at Sundance", 116p. (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - "K. 589", screenplay by Eugenia Zukerman and Helen Whitney, l982, 111p. (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Summary of "Rescue in Denmark", a history work by Harold Flender, l96l. 23p. (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - "Hemingway: The Wind, The Land and The Sea", treatment and screenplay ("First Draft-English version"), by Jose Garcia, 1986. Incomplete: 34p. (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - "The Gun", teleplay for "Lassie" TV series Jackson Gillis, l954, various pagings and annotations, incl. other script materials related to the series. (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - "Parodies Lost", mimeographed poems by Paul Jarrico, various dates. 5p. (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Two typed poems by Genny Lim and Guy Michel, July l984. (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Biographical and professional information, clippings, theater programs, etc, regarding stage director Larry Loonin, 1976-79. (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Five theatrical sketches and stories by Robert R. Presnell, [Stanford University], 1935. Typed scripts, with annotations, various pagings. (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - "Hallelujah!", story by Wilma Shore. Typed script, n.d. 19p. (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - "Maria la O (Mary My Own)": scene outline for musical comedy in two acts, by Ernesto Lecuona. Typed script, n.d. 7p. (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - Music sheets for songs "Johnny's Gone" (music by Earl Robinson and lyrics by W.Salt) and "The People Painter" (music by Earl Robinson); poem by Earl Robinson. 3 items. (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - SLIDES
      - Slides taken in Spain (bullfight, Cordoba), and Connecticut, [1974]. 83 slides. (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Slides taken in Spain (Barcelona); slides of W.Salt, family and friends, [1974]. 127 slides. (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Slides taken in Guatemala, 1975. 77 slides. (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Slides taken in W.Salt's home in Connecticut, [1970s]. 70 slides. (See box 108-2) (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Slides taken in Spain, Italy and France, [1965?]. 78 slides. (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - WRITINGS BY WALDO SALT
      - "An Oceanic Cosmogony. Compiled by W.M.Salt", Stanford University, 1931. Typed script with pen and ink drawings. (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Poems and lyrics, typed and hand-written, mostly undated. More than 30. (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - "Apologia Pro Vita Sua. Anonymous", Culver City, l938. Typed script. Two copies (3p) and a different version (4p). (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - "Da Vinci and the Vatican", article by W.Salt clipped from "NM" [magazine], 10/2/45. (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Memorial speech in honor of Arnold Manoff, incl. notes. Typed and hand-written script, undated. 9 items. (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Memorial speech in honor of Dr.Murray Abowitz, incl. newspaper clipping, [1981]. (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Typed and hand-written notes on LSD experience, undated. 4 items. (Box 114, Folder 9)